Misery loves family.
Meet the Fockers is a comedy, romance film directed by Jay Roach.
Hard-to-crack ex-CIA man Jack Byrnes and his wife Dina head for the warmer climes of
Florida to meet the parents of their son-in-law-to-be, Greg Focker.
Unlike their happily matched offspring, the future in-laws find themselves
in a situation of opposites that definitely do not attract.
Greg Focker, played by Ben Stiller.
Jack Byrnes, played by Robert De Niro.
Bernie Focker, played by Dustin Hoffman.
Rozalin Focker, played by Barbra Streisand.
Dina Byrnes, played by Blythe Danner.
Pam Byrnes, played by Teri Polo.
Meet the Fockers is a 2004 American romantic comedy film directed by Jay Roach.
The second in the Fockers film series, it features Robert De Niro, Ben Stiller, Blythe Danner and Teri Polo reprising their
roles from the first film, with Dustin Hoffman and Barbra Streisand joining the cast as Greg Focker's parents.
Meet the Fockers was released on December 22, 2004, in
the United States by Universal Pictures.
It received mixed reviews, and was a box-office success, grossing $522
million and becoming the seventh-highest-grossing film of 2004.
A further sequel, Little Fockers, followed in 2010.
The film explores themes of florida, central intelligence agency (cia),
nurse, parent child relationship, anti-authoritarian upbringing.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.